# PERSONAL PROFILE

I am an undergraduate at DigiPen Institute of Technology pursuing a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science in Real-Time Interactive Simulation. I have multiple relevant experience in gameplay programming / game engine architecture and harbor a deep passion for developing games and applications!

### SKILLS

- (++
- C
- C#
- Unity
- Machine Learning
- Python
- Jupyter
- ReactJS
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- OpenGL
- ImGui

# AWARDS

Mind Over Matter - Winner for Best 2D Visual Design (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best Sophomore Game (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best 2D Graphics Technology (DigiPen)

Mind Over Matter - Finalist for Best User Interface (DigiPen)

FishieProtecc - Finalist for Gumi Asia's Best Freshman Game (DigiPen)

Dean's Honor List throughout 2018 - 2021 (DigiPen)

# YOU CAN FIND ME AT



https://weixianglim.github.io/

in linkedin.com/in/weixiang-lim

# WEI XIANG LIM

# ASPIRING GAMES PROGRAMMER AND DEVELOPER

## RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

### **TEACHING ASSISTANT**

DigiPen Institute of Technology | Feb 2018 - Mar 2021

- Assisted professors in grading, guiding and teaching (Math, CS)
- Held TA sessions for students after curriculum
- Provided private consultations for students

### PROGRAMMING INTERN

Neeuro | Sep 2015 - Nov 2015

- Developed part of the Memorie app with the existing Neeuro team
- Created minigames in Unity Engine for Memorie
- Fully developed a sister prototype application with Unity Engine
- Worked with and tested Neeuro's SenzeBand technology

### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

### DIGIPEN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

BS in Computer Science Real-Time Interactive Simulation

- Studied advanced C++ and various programming techniques
- Held the technical lead role for 4 game projects
- Built 2D & 3D custom game engines

### NANYANG POLYTECHNIC

Diploma in Digital Entertainment Technology | 2014 - 2016

- NYP Scholarship holder
- Studied extensive C++
- · Worked with popular industry game engines
- Studied various games development techniques
- Introduced to PlayStation 4 multicore development